st-minver.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Notice

The effective date of this Privacy Notice is September 1, 2015

## Our commitment to you

As a world's leading end-to-end gaming company, International Game Technology, PLC and its subsidiaries (“IGT”) is committed to data privacy, and we recognize the responsibility we have to protect the privacy rights of all individuals whose personal information is within our custody and management in accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations.

As used in this Privacy Notice, terms such as “we” or “our” or “us” refer to IGT and its current and future subsidiaries.

The term “personal information” used throughout this policy means any information relating directly or indirectly to a specific individual. Personal Information includes, among other information, an individual’s name, postal address, email address, telephone number, and credential information. Please note that although personal information is used throughout this document, “personal data” would have the same meaning and as such could replace the term “personal information”.

We may revise this Privacy Notice from time to time as we deem appropriate consistent with the principles described in this notice, our commitment to you, our evolving business needs, or changes in applicable laws or regulations. Please check this Privacy Notice frequently to ensure that you are in agreement with any change.

## The purpose and applicability of this Privacy Notice

The purpose of this Privacy Notice is to describe how we handle your personal information as well as other information received through the igt.com website and we encourage you to read this Privacy Notice carefully before using this website. This Privacy Notice, along with the website Terms and Conditions, describe the conditions of use under which we offer you access to our services. By using our services you signify your agreement to this Privacy Notice.

This Privacy Notice does not apply to information collected through others means such as telephone or in person.

This website may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the security, privacy practices, or the content of such websites. Once you leave this website, using any of these links, the privacy practices mentioned in this notice do not apply and we invite you to examine the privacy statements and the Terms and Conditions that govern the other websites.

## Information we collect about you

This website includes webpages asking you to provide us with your personal information in order to respond to your request for services or information. You do not have to provide us with your personal information; however, we may limit your ability to use or to request certain services or information.

We will not intentionally collect personal information that is not relevant to the uses stated in this notice.

### Personal information

We collect your first and last names, email address, company, phone number, and your comments under the Contact Us webpage in order to answer your request. We also collect your email address under the Investor Relations webpage to provide you with email alerts.

We collect your login credentials (email address or username and password) under the Gaming Support webpage if you have an account with us and login into it. Please note that such accounts are intended solely for IGT customers and employees - those in the gaming industry who work directly with IGT. When registering for a member account, we may collect among other information:

  * Your company including country, region, city and name
  * Your contact information including first, middle and last names, title and job title, department, landline, mobile phone and fax numbers
  * A quality password and the reason for access from a drop list

Please note that other third party websites may collect your personal information when you apply for and submit a job application and when you request gaming support. The privacy practices mentioned in this notice do not apply and we invite you to examine the privacy statements and the Terms and Conditions that govern the other websites.

### Information from web technologies

We use other web technologies, which may include “Cookies” and other web technologies to gather information that also help us understand how you use our website. A cookie is a small text file composed of letters and numbers that is stored on your computing device. A cookie may be persistent in order to keep your profile and preferences or may expire at the end of a web session. In particular, we use non-persistent cookies which expire at the end of the browser session to determine your usage of this website. We track activities of our logged-in account members. We may also use click events on certain graphics and data attributes.

Your computer devices may allow you to disable cookies and similar web artifacts by setting your browser preferences at any time; however, we may require the use of these web technologies to enable us for instance to establish the connection between your device and this website or to personalize and improve your experience and the site navigation.

### Information from monitoring tools

We use the default capabilities of your browser as well as those used by Google Analytics and New Relic monitoring tools to collect anonymous information about your usage of this website. By visiting this website, we will automatically gather and store the following information including, but not limited to the following:

  * Internet Protocol (“IP”) address and domain name of the device you are using when browsing this website. The IP address is a dynamic or static numerical identifier assigned either to an Internet Service Provider (“ISP”) or directly to a person’s computer
  * Type of browser and operating system you are using
  * Date and time of your visit on this website
  * Webpages or services accessed at this website

Google Analytics and New Relic record visitor traffic but does honor your browser cookie blocking setting.

## How we use information we collect about you

We may use your information for purposes such as:

  * To respond and/or follow up on your request
  * To alert you with news releases when you subscribe
  * To create your member account and provide you with gaming support
  * To improve your website experience and customize our services we provide to you
  * To comply with applicable laws and regulations or to respond to a public authority request
  * To protect our rights or the integrity of this website

We may also de-identify, combine, or aggregate any of the information we collect for analyzing usage statistics and trends.

We will not use your personal information for purposes that are incompatible with the purposes for which we originally received your information without your express consent.

We will retain your information only as long as you are a registered member of this website or use our services and as necessary for us to comply with a public authority, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and as otherwise reasonably necessary for our business purposes including but not limited to compliance with all applicable laws and regulations.

## With who we may share information about you

We will not sell or lease your personal information to third parties without your consent.

We may disclose your information to IGT affiliates as well as NTT Data, (add)ventures, and Masterminds who work on our behalf and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this Privacy Notice. We may also disclose your information to other business partners such as NASDAQ.

We may disclose your information to other entities in the event IGT goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, as your personal information might be among the assets transferred.

We may also disclose your information when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or the integrity of the website, prevent harm to other visitors or protect your safety, investigate fraud or breaches of a contract or a law, or respond to a legal process or a request from a public authority.

We may store your information in our facilities such as but not limited to Reno for support activities as well as on Amazon Web Services located in Portland, Oregon, U.S.A and Dublin, Ireland to facilitate your connectivity by accessing our services from multiple devices, anytime, anywhere.

Please note that when you are visiting this website from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, the exchange of information between your location and this website will necessarily result in a cross border transfer of that information. By visiting and providing information to this website, you consent to the processing and transfer of your data across international boundaries.

## How do we protect your information

We have reasonable and customary security measures in place to protect against unauthorized access, use, and disclosure of your personal information. As an example of such measures, we restrict access to personal information on a need to know basis.

To protect the confidentiality, integrity, availability of your personal information in our custody, we maintain physical, logical, and procedural safeguards in compliance with internationally recognized standards and other industry based security best practices. As part of these best practices, we are reviewing our privacy policies on a regular basis to ensure our compliance with data protection laws and regulations of the jurisdictions in which we do business.

As an example of such compliance, our U.S. entity, IGT Global Solution Corporation, abides by the voluntary Safe Harbor Principles managed by the U.S. Department of Commerce for the collection, use, and retention of personal information from countries in the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and Switzerland. To learn more about the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Program and view our certification, please visit <http://export.gov/safeharbor/index.asp>.

## What can you do about the information that we collect and handle

First and foremost, you need to agree with the terms as set forth in this Privacy Notice along with our Terms and Conditions.

Within reasonable limits on expenses and frequency requests, we will allow you to view or get a copy of the information we are holding about you, or request changes to correct any information we are holding about you that you believe is inaccurate or incomplete.

You may submit your request in writing to; email or call us at the postal or electronic addresses or phone number as indicated in this Privacy Notice. We will promptly correct any incomplete or inaccurate information or in the event your request was denied, communicate the reason for the denial and generate a written record of that request and the reason(s) for denial.

If you choose not to agree with these terms or you choose to cease your membership at a later time, we may limit your ability to receive certain services or information.

## How you can contact us

If you have any concern about this Privacy Notice or our privacy practices, please contact us:

International Game Technology PLC (IGT)  
66 Seymour Street  
London, U.K. WH1 5BT 

Phone +44 02075353200  
Email: [privacy@igt.com](mailto:privacy@igt.com?Subject=Privacy%20Notice)
